# Hossein Azami

Istanbul, Turkey

hossein.azami@gmail.com



+905526278675



linkedin.com/in/hossein-azami-7b90a3189



https://azami.ir

### Summary

Experienced Back end Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Software Project Management, Software Design, ASP.NET MVC, C# Programming, .NET Framework, ASP.NET Core, ASP.NET Web API, Angular, Balzor and SignalR. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Information Technology from Meybod Azad University.

## **Experience**



#### ■ Web Developer

Pasargad Machinery and Equipment Leasing Company

Feb 2010 - Mar 2011 (1 year 2 months)

Implementation of online rental payment system

# ■ Web Developer

Tajeran Pishro

Sep 2004 - Jan 2006 (1 year 5 months)

Amazon and Target store site template for selling Iranian products in the Middle East

# Senior Project Manager

Negin Resaneh Mihan Co.

Mar 2008 - May 2010 (2 years 3 months)

- -Production of daily bulletin production system
- -Apply mobna.com site to promote mobile phones
- -Build a news search engine based on Crawling

### 🕠 Senior Project Manager

Respina Radyn IT Co.

Sep 2010 - Jan 2020 (9 years 5 months)

I have immigrated to Turkey

### Web Developer

Tehran Municipality ICT Organization

Feb 2008 - Mar 2011 (3 years 2 months)

- -Tehran Municipality project control and management system implementation
- -Tehran Municipality Urban Development Project

#### **Software Architect**

Gostaresh Informatic Iranian

Jun 2005 - Mar 2007 (1 year 10 months) Implementation of online regulation and payment system for Tosee Insurance company

# Application Developer

Tadvin Farayand Co.

Feb 2005 - May 2005 (4 months)

Purchasing system and purchasing tracking from Tadvin financial and administrative systems set

## ■ Web Developer

Pishgaman Isatis

Mar 2004 - Oct 2004 (8 months)

Parnian Madrese Smart School Project in Yazd

### **Education**

# Meybod Azad University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Hardware Engineering 2001 - 2005

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



🌀 **C**# - SoloLearn

1080-17810338

### **Skills**

C# • ASP.NET Core • SignalR • ASP.NET Web API • Node.js • GitHub • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • AngularJS